{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "GirisMesajimiz",
            "answer": "Hi Sanofian ! I am Hopkins, How's your day going? You can ask me anything that comes to your mind.",
            "answer2": "You can choose your language from the settings tab.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "Welcome Message",
            "answer": "Hi Sanofian ! I am Hopkins, How's your day going? You can ask me anything that comes to your mind.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hosgeldin Mesaji",
            "answer": "Merhaba Sanofi'li ! Ben Hopkins, gÃ¼nÃ¼n nasÄ±l geÃ§iyor ? AklÄ±na ne gelirse bana sorabilirsin.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "training",
            "answer": "https://sanofi-learning.csod.com/",
            "answer2": "You can access your trainings from iLearn",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "folder",
            "answer": "https://sanofiservices.service-now.com/onesupport",
            "answer2": "You should contact your location's IT support for this issue and start a ticket from One Support",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "visa",
            "answer": "https://sanofiservices.service-now.com/onesupport?id=kb_article&table=kb_knowledge&sysparm_article=KB0150739",
            "answer2": "Where is your journey my friend? Please don't forget to bring me chocolate from wherever you go ðŸ™‚. You can find the documents you will need when getting a visa from this article. ",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "abbreviation",
            "answer": "GBU is an abbreviation for global business unit that is used in Sanofi regularly.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "watch",
            "answer": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/fjF7NWqLc-0?autoplay=1&mute=1&controls=0&showinfo=0&rel=0&modestbranding=1&fs=1",
            "answer2": "Have you watched this video in which our country's leader Cem Ã–ztÃ¼rk is a guest on Onedio channel? If you haven't watched it, I recommend you watch it. Enjoy it ðŸ™‚",
            "tipi":"video"
        },
        {
            "question": "title",
            "answer": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9pprUJeEHCs?autoplay=1&mute=1&controls=0&showinfo=0&rel=0&modestbranding=1&fs=1",
            "answer2": "You can watch this video about LEAP Interns. If you cannot find an answer to the question in your mind, you can ask me again.",
            "tipi":"video"

        },
        {
            "question": "eÄŸitim",
            "answer": "https://sanofi-learning.csod.com/",
            "answer2": "EÄŸitimlerine iLearn Ã¼zerinden eriÅŸebilirsin",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "dosya",
            "answer": "https://sanofiservices.service-now.com/onesupport",
            "answer2": "BulunduÄŸun lokasyondaki IT departmanÄ± ile iletiÅŸime geÃ§ip ticket aÃ§abilirsin.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "vize",
            "answer": "https://sanofiservices.service-now.com/onesupport?id=kb_article&table=kb_knowledge&sysparm_article=KB0150739",
            "answer2": "Yolculuk nereye arkadaÅŸÄ±m ? GittiÄŸin yerden bana Ã§ikolata getirmeyi unutma ðŸ™‚. Vize alÄ±rken ihtiyacÄ±n olacak belgelere bu makaleden ulaÅŸabilirsin. ",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "kÄ±saltma",
            "answer": "GBU, Sanofi'de dÃ¼zenli olarak kullanÄ±lan kÃ¼resel iÅŸ biriminin kÄ±saltmasÄ±dÄ±r.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "izle",
            "answer": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/fjF7NWqLc-0?autoplay=1&mute=1&controls=0&showinfo=0&rel=0&modestbranding=1&fs=1",
            "answer2": "Ãœlkemizin lideri Cem Ã–ztÃ¼rk'Ã¼n Onedio kanalÄ±na konuk olduÄŸu bu videoyu izledin mi? EÄŸer izlemediysen izlemeni tavsiye ederim. TadÄ±nÄ± Ã§Ä±kar ðŸ™‚",
            "tipi":"video"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ã¼nvan",
            "answer": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9pprUJeEHCs?autoplay=1&mute=1&controls=0&showinfo=0&rel=0&modestbranding=1&fs=1",
            "answer2": "LEAP stajyerleri ile ilgili bu videoyu izleyebilirsin. AklÄ±ndaki soruya yanÄ±t bulamazsan bana tekrardan soru sorabilirsin.",
            "tipi":"video"
        },
        {
            "question": "selam",
            "answer": "Selam dostum.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "hi",
            "answer": "Hi buddy!",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "merhaba",
            "answer": "Merhaba ! Seni gÃ¶rdÃ¼ÄŸÃ¼me sevindim.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "hello",
            "answer": "Hello ! I'm glad to see you",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "nasÄ±lsÄ±n",
            "answer": "Her zamanki gibi sÃ¼perim. Sen de sÃ¼per gÃ¶rÃ¼nÃ¼yorsun.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "how are you",
            "answer": "I'm great as always. You look great too.",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "adÄ±n",
            "answer": "Ben Hopkins !",
            "tipi":"text"
        },
        {
            "question": "Name",
            "answer": "I'm Hopkins !",
            "tipi":"text"
        }
    ],
    "defaultAnswerTR": "Ne dediÄŸini anlayamadÄ±m. Daha fazla detay verir misin ?",
    "defaultAnswerEN": "I didn't understand what you said sorry. Can you give more details ?"
  }

  